<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<translations>
    <en>
        <heading>Welcome to ClimateSight</heading>
        <subheading>What is it about?</subheading>
        <content>
            Welcome to our Climate Change Impact Viewer! Our project aims to raise awareness about the
            significant impacts of climate change on our planet. Through interactive maps and data visualization,
            we provide a platform for users to explore and understand the various effects of climate change, from
            rising sea levels to changing weather patterns. With the help of cutting-edge technologies, we aim to
            make complex climate data accessible and engaging for everyone. Our mission is to empower individuals
            and communities to take action against climate change and contribute to building a sustainable future
            for generations to come. Join us in our journey to explore the impacts of climate change and take
            meaningful steps towards a greener and more resilient planet!
        </content>
    </en>
    <de>
        <heading>Willkommen bei ClimateSight</heading>
        <subheading>Was ist unser Ziel?</subheading>
        <content>
            Willkommen bei unserem Climate Change Impact Viewer! Unser Projekt zielt darauf ab, das Bewusstsein für
            die erheblichen Auswirkungen des Klimawandels auf unseren Planeten zu schärfen. Durch interaktive
            Karten und Datenvisualisierung bieten wir den Nutzern eine Plattform, um die verschiedenen Auswirkungen
            des Klimawandels zu erforschen und zu verstehen, vom steigenden Meeresspiegel bis hin zu sich verändernden
            Wettermustern. Mit Hilfe modernster Technologien wollen wir komplexe Klimadaten für jedermann zugänglich
            und interessant machen. Unser Ziel ist es, Einzelpersonen und Gemeinschaften zu befähigen, Maßnahmen gegen
            den Klimawandel zu ergreifen und zum Aufbau einer nachhaltigen Zukunft für kommende Generationen beizutragen.
            Begleiten Sie uns auf unserer Reise, um die Auswirkungen des Klimawandels zu erforschen und sinnvolle
            Schritte in Richtung eines grüneren und widerstandsfähigeren Planeten zu unternehmen!
        </content>
    </de>
</translations>
